Hi everyone! Welcome to this how to style golf pants video. I have three totally
different pants or trousers and I'm going to show you one everyday
streetwear look and one clubbing look for each of them. For this video I teamed
up with Demolite UK. They provided me with the pants so thank you Demolite!
Therefore I have to label this video as advertisement. I'm super excited about
some of the looks. I think they turned out really good and I definitely have a
favorite one. Maybe I'll tell you at the end which one it is. This is the first
pant. It's a PVC kind of jeans with pockets at back and front and there is
some velvet part or inlay at the inner side of the leg. For the street style look I
paired it with this printed shirt. It's a buffo cat you know and by the way cat
Hello! Meet Nono, she's my guest again and I'm cat sitting her. She was sleeping and I woke
her up. But yeah, there she goes again. For the clavie look I chose this velvet crop
top. Velvet because the velvet partner pants I thought it's going to match really
good and it did. Have a look now at these looks.
Thank you.
pants it's a black jeans and there is a pocket at the side of the leg which is
integrated with a lot of metal details and at the end of the leg there is
another detail with kind of shiny fake fabric.
with shiny fabric. The street style look features this awesome jacket by
Ischnittmuskel. It's handmade and with a lot of details. And the clubbing look is
with a mesh shirt but have a look yourself.
Thank you.
And number three are these fake leather ones.
pretty cool although I think I have to wear a belt because it's a bit too wide
at the hemline for me. From the street style look it's a tunic I bought in Morocco
last week and I paired it with a harness. You'll see this corset in the clubbing
look with the pants they go pretty well together and this is the only corset in
all of the looks so don't miss it.
Thank you.
I
enjoyed these looks. My personal favorite was the fake leather leggings with the
corset, the mesh top and the bra. I think it looks pretty badass. I hope I could
give you some inspiration for styling leggings for every occasion. Hope you
enjoyed this video, have a good day and bye!